Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-2004; 213494
  - Zuka -- The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery, 1 of 3), 1985-1989; cuid2896; 213840 (Box I:10, Folder 20)
  - Zuka -- The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery, 2 of 3), 1986-1989; cuid2897; 213839 (Box I:10, Folder 21)
  - Zuka -- The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery, 3 of 3), 1988; cuid2898; 213838 (Box I:10, Folder 22)
  - Mike Bidlo (Window Installation in Conj. with Warhol Exhibit), 1988; cuid2899; 213837 (Box I:10, Folder 23)
  - Robert Morris -- Proposal and Other Preliminary Material (1 of 2), 1986-1988; cuid2900; 213836 (Box I:10, Folder 24)
  - Robert Morris -- Proposal and Other Preliminary Material (2 of 2), 1986-1989; cuid2901; 213835 (Box I:10, Folder 25)
  - Robert Morris -- Correspondence, 1989 January 26-February 2; cuid2902; 213834 (Box I:10, Folder 26)
  - Robert Morris -- Press Release, 1989 April 21; cuid2903; 213833 (Box I:10, Folder 27)
  - Robert Morris -- Check List, Undated; cuid2904; 213832 (Box I:10, Folder 28)
  - Robert Morris -- Wall Text, 1989 May 8; cuid2905; 213831 (Box I:10, Folder 29)
  - Robert Morris -- Installation, 1989 March-April; cuid2906; 213830 (Box I:10, Folder 30)
  - Robert Morris -- Catalogue (1 of 3), 1989 March-April; cuid2907; 213829 (Box I:10, Folder 31)
  - Robert Morris -- Catalogue (2 of 3), Circa 1988-1989; cuid2908; 213828 (Box I:10, Folder 32)
  - Robert Morris -- Catalogue (3 of 3), 1989; cuid2909; 213827 (Box I:10, Folder 33)
  - Robert Morris -- Reviews, Notices, 1989 May-October; cuid2910; 213826 (Box I:10, Folder 34)
  - Bernard Frize -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Robert Morris), Circa 1989; cuid2911; 213825 (Box I:10, Folder 35)
  - Tom Hardy and Steve Ausbury (Treasures of the Bastille), Circa 1989; cuid2912; 213824 (Box I:10, Folder 36)
  - Weegee -- Exhibit Material, Undated; cuid2913; 213823 (Box I:10, Folder 37)
  - Weegee -- Press, 1989 September-November; cuid2914; 213822 (Box I:10, Folder 38)
  - Ching Ho Cheng -- Wall Text, Circa 1989; cuid2915; 213821 (Box I:11, Folder 1)
  - Peter Levinson (Window Installation and Small Gallery), Circa 1989; cuid2916; 213820 (Box I:11, Folder 2)
  - Excommunication -- Press Release, 1989 November 8; cuid2917; 213819 (Box I:11, Folder 3)
  - Excommunication -- Text, Circa 1989; cuid2918; 213818 (Box I:11, Folder 4)
  - Excommunication -- Text and Other Miscellaneous, 1989; cuid2919; 213817 (Box I:11, Folder 5)
  - Excommunication -- Border Arts Workshop, 1989 September-1990 January; cuid2920; 213816 (Box I:11, Folder 6)
  - Excommunication -- Rick Bolton, 1989; cuid2921; 213815 (Box I:11, Folder 7)
  - Excommunication -- Steve Evans, Circa 1989; cuid2922; 213814 (Box I:11, Folder 8)
  - Excommunication -- The Jewish Museum, 1987-1989; cuid2923; 213813 (Box I:11, Folder 9)
  - Excommunication -- Hillary Leone, Circa 1989; cuid2924; 213812 (Box I:11, Folder 10)
  - Excommunication -- Bernice Steinbaum Gallery, Circa 1989; cuid2925; 213811 (Box I:11, Folder 11)
  - Excommunication -- Mitra Tabrizian, 1989; cuid2926; 213810 (Box I:11, Folder 12)
  - Excommunication -- Mark Wallinger (Anthony Reynolds Gallery), 1986-1988; cuid2927; 213809 (Box I:11, Folder 13)
  - Excommunication -- Press, 1989 November-1990 January; cuid2928; 213808 (Box I:11, Folder 14)
  - Excommunication -- Miscellaneous, 1986-1989; cuid2929; 213807 (Box I:11, Folder 15)
  - Judite Dos Santos -- Aids Project (Missing/Desaparecidos), 1988-1989; cuid2930; 213806 (Box I:11, Folder 16)
  - Myrel Chernick, 1989 January-July; cuid2931; 213805 (Box I:11, Folder 17)
  - Hujar -- Timeline and Biograpahy, 1989 November; cuid2932; 213804 (Box I:11, Folder 18)
  - Hujar -- List, Undated; cuid2933; 213803 (Box I:11, Folder 19)
  - Hujar -- Catalogue, 1989-1990; cuid2934; 213802 (Box I:11, Folder 20)
  - Hujar -- Press Releases, 1990 January 16; cuid2935; 213801 (Box I:11, Folder 21)
  - Hujar -- Press (1 of 2), 1991 February; cuid2936; 213800 (Box I:11, Folder 22)
  - Hujar -- Press (2 of 2), 1990 February-September; cuid2937; 213799 (Box I:11, Folder 23)
  - Hujar -- Press Photos, 1990 February-1991 June; cuid2938; 213798 (Box I:11, Folder 24)
  - Hujar -- Mounted Image, Undated; cuid2939; 213797 (Box I:11, Folder 25)
  - Hujar -- Traveling Exhibition, 1990 January-July; cuid2940; 213796 (Box I:11, Folder 26)
  - Gernard Richter -- Background, 1990; cuid2941; 213795 (Box I:11, Folder 27)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Correspondence, 1989 September-1990 February; cuid2942; 213794 (Box I:11, Folder 28)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Catalogue, Circa 1989-1990; cuid2943; 213793 (Box I:11, Folder 29)
  - Gerhard Richter -- ICA and Other Venues, 1989 August-1990 February; cuid2944; 213792 (Box I:11, Folder 30)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Press (1 of 3), 1989 February-December; cuid2945; 213791 (Box I:11, Folder 31)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Press (2 of 3), 1989 November-1990 October; cuid2946; 213790 (Box I:11, Folder 32)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Press (3 of 3), 1989 May-1990 October; cuid2947; 213789 (Box I:11, Folder 33)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Publicity Packet, 1989-1990; cuid2948; 213788 (Box I:11, Folder 34)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Reviews (1 of 2), 1990 March-1995 July; cuid2949; 213787 (Box I:11, Folder 35)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Reviews (2 of 2), 1990 April-1995 July; cuid2950; 213786 (Box I:11, Folder 36)
  - Barbara Strasen, 1990 February-May; cuid2951; 213785 (Box I:11, Folder 37)
  - Paysage Demoralise: Landscape at the End of the Century -- Condition, 1990 May; cuid2952; 213784 (Box I:11, Folder 38)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Press Release and Publicity, 1990 April; cuid2953; 213783 (Box I:11, Folder 39)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Press, 1990 June; cuid2954; 213782 (Box I:11, Folder 40)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Helen Chadwick, 1987-1990; cuid2955; 213781 (Box I:11, Folder 41)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Graeme Murray Gallery/John Weber, Findlay, Goldsworthy, Cooper, 1987 August-1990 April; cuid2956; 213780 (Box I:11, Folder 42)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Miscellaneous, 1987-1990; cuid2957; 213779 (Box I:11, Folder 43)
  - Peter Sebok -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Paysage Demoralise, 1 of 2), 1989; cuid2958; 213778 (Box I:11, Folder 44)
  - Peter Sebok -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Paysage Demoralise, 2 of 2), 1989-1992; cuid2959; 213777 (Box I:11, Folder 45)
  - Against Nature: Japanese Art in the Eighties -- Proposal, 1987-1988; cuid2960; 213776 (Box I:11, Folder 46)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Catalogue and Exhibit Roundtable Discussion, Circa 1989-1990; cuid2961; 213775 (Box I:11, Folder 47)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Labels, Circa 1989-1990; cuid2962; 213774 (Box I:11, Folder 48)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Color Xeroxes, Circa 1988-1990; cuid2963; 213773 (Box I:11, Folder 49)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Initial Schedule and Slide List, Circa 1989-1990; cuid2964; 213772 (Box I:11, Folder 50)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Installation, 1990; cuid2965; 213771 (Box I:11, Folder 51)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- John's Installation Notes, 1989 March-June; cuid2966; 213770 (Box I:11, Folder 52)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- General Unnamed Sheets (Lists), 1989 January-June; cuid2967; 213769 (Box I:11, Folder 53)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type (1 of 2), 1988 June-1991 September; cuid2968; 213768 (Box I:11, Folder 54)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type (2 of 2), 1988 July-1991 April; cuid2969; 213767 (Box I:11, Folder 55)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumbtype Correspondence, 1989 September-October; cuid2970; 213766 (Box I:11, Folder 56)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type "PH" VHS, 1990; cuid2971; 213765 (Box I:12, Folder 1)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Releases, 1990 August 16; cuid2972; 213764 (Box I:12, Folder 2)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Photos Information, 1989 July-1991 January; cuid2973; 213763 (Box I:12, Folder 3)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Toshikatu Endo, 1987-1990; cuid2974; 213762 (Box I:12, Folder 4)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Shoko Maemoto, 1990 January; cuid2975; 213761 (Box I:12, Folder 5)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Masami Teraoka, 1990; cuid2976; 213760 (Box I:12, Folder 6)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Noboru Tsubaki, 1986; cuid2977; 213759 (Box I:12, Folder 7)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press, 1988-1990; cuid2978; 213758 (Box I:12, Folder 8)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Information, 1989 January-June; cuid2979; 213757 (Box I:12, Folder 9)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum Press, 1989 July-December; cuid2980; 213756 (Box I:12, Folder 10)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Boston Press, 1989 December; cuid2981; 213755 (Box I:12, Folder 11)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Grey Gallery Press (1 of 2), 1990 June-October; cuid2982; 213754 (Box I:12, Folder 12)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Grey Gallery Press (2 of 2), 1990 September-1991 February; cuid2983; 213753 (Box I:12, Folder 13)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- San Francisco Press, 1989 March-July; cuid2984; 213752 (Box I:12, Folder 14)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Reviews and Notices, 1988 June-1990 August; cuid2985; 213751 (Box I:12, Folder 15)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum, 1989 September-October; cuid2986; 213750 (Box I:12, Folder 16)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Contemporary Art Museum, Houston (Miscellaneous), 1990 October-December; cuid2987; 213749 (Box I:12, Folder 17)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Seattle Art Museum, 1990 March-May; cuid2988; 213748 (Box I:12, Folder 18)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Yasumasa Morimura, 1991 September-1992 April; cuid2989; 213747 (Box I:12, Folder 19)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Japan Society News, 1988 March-November; cuid2990; 213746 (Box I:12, Folder 20)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Artist and Exhibit Material, 1986-1990; cuid2991; 213745 (Box I:12, Folder 21)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Clippings (1 of 2), 1987 April-1989 July; cuid2992; 213744 (Box I:12, Folder 22)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Clippings (2 of 2), 1983 June-1988 November; cuid2993; 213743 (Box I:12, Folder 23)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Printed Material (1 of 2), 1983-1988; cuid2994; 213742 (Box I:12, Folder 24)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Printed Material (2 of 2), 1958-1988; cuid2995; 213741 (Box I:12, Folder 25)
  - The Greeks and the Sea (Small Gallery, Nov. 12-20, 1990), cuid2996; 213740 (Box I:12, Folder 26)
  - Mabou Mines -- Preliminary Work, Circa 1980-1991; cuid2997; 213739 (Box I:12, Folder 27)
  - Mabou Mines -- Installation, 1990 October-1991 January; cuid2998; 213738 (Box I:12, Folder 28)
  - Mabou Mines -- Drafts, Labels and Other Miscellaneous, 1976-1991; cuid2999; 213737 (Box I:12, Folder 29)
  - Mabou Mines -- Video Sleeve, 1990; cuid3000; 213736 (Box I:12, Folder 30)
  - Mabou Mines -- Press (1 of 2), 1980 December-1990 December; cuid3001; 213735 (Box I:12, Folder 31)
  - Mabou Mines -- Press (2 of 2), 1990 May; cuid3002; 213734 (Box I:12, Folder 32)
  - Tom Wolf and Ken Chu (Small Gallery/WSW), Circa 1990-1991; cuid3003; 213733 (Box I:12, Folder 33)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Installation, 1990-1991; cuid3004; 213732 (Box I:12, Folder 34)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Press, 1991 January-February; cuid3005; 213731 (Box I:12, Folder 35)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Miscellaneous, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3006; 213730 (Box I:12, Folder 36)
  - Minnette Lehmann, 1988 January-1991 January; cuid3007; 213729 (Box I:12, Folder 37)
  - Permanent Collection, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3008; 213728 (Box I:12, Folder 38)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Checklists, 1991; cuid3009; 213727 (Box I:12, Folder 39)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Artists, 1990-1992; cuid3010; 213726 (Box I:12, Folder 40)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Artists CV's, 1991; cuid3011; 213725 (Box I:12, Folder 41)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Rasheed Araeen, 1991 June; cuid3012; 213724 (Box I:12, Folder 42)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Rebecca Belmore, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3013; 213723 (Box I:12, Folder 43)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Nadine Chan, 1991 January-1992 October; cuid3014; 213722 (Box I:12, Folder 44)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Albert Chong, 1991 June-November; cuid3015; 213721 (Box I:12, Folder 45)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Allan DeSouza, Circa 1991-1993; cuid3016; 213720 (Box I:12, Folder 46)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Jamelie Hassan, 1991 February-1993 May; cuid3017; 213719 (Box I:12, Folder 47)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Mona Hatoum, 1990 January-1993 April; cuid3018; 213718 (Box I:12, Folder 48)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Roshini Kempadoo, 1991 January-July; cuid3019; 213717 (Box I:12, Folder 49)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Glenn Ligon/Emily Fisher Landay, 1991 June-1992; cuid3020; 213716 (Box I:12, Folder 50)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Whitfield Lovell, 1990 December-Circa 1992; cuid3021; 213715 (Box I:12, Folder 51)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Lani Maestro, 1991 February-1993 April; cuid3022; 213714 (Box I:12, Folder 52)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Lillian Mulero, 1990 December-1991 January; cuid3023; 213713 (Box I:12, Folder 53)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Ming Mur-Ray, 1990 December-1992 April; cuid3024; 213712 (Box I:12, Folder 54)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Keith Piper, 1990 January-October; cuid3025; 213711 (Box I:12, Folder 55)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Ingrid Pollard, 1990 November-1992 October; cuid3026; 213710 (Box I:12, Folder 56)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Donald Rodney/Art Council Collection, 1991 July-December; cuid3027; 213709 (Box I:12, Folder 57)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Yinka Shonibare, 1990 October 19; cuid3028; 213708 (Box I:12, Folder 58)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Simmons/Janelle Reiring Metro Pictures, 1989 December-1990 April; cuid3029; 213707 (Box I:12, Folder 59)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Black Artists File, 1985-1990; cuid3030; 213706 (Box I:13, Folder 1)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists, 1989-1990; cuid3031; 213705 (Box I:13, Folder 2)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (In Show), 1985 April-1991 September; cuid3032; 213704 (Box I:13, Folder 3)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Not Included), 1990 June-December; cuid3033; 213703 (Box I:13, Folder 4)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Mulero), 1991; cuid3034; 213702 (Box I:13, Folder 5)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Gary Simmons), 1989 December-1990 August; cuid3035; 213701 (Box I:13, Folder 6)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Glenn Ligon), 1991 July 29; cuid3036; 213700 (Box I:13, Folder 7)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists, 1988-1991 October; cuid3037; 213699 (Box I:13, Folder 8)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Rasheed Araaen), 1990 November-1992 October; cuid3038; 213698 (Box I:13, Folder 9)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Roshini Kempadoo), 1990-1991; cuid3039; 213697 (Box I:13, Folder 10)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Jamilie Hassan), 1984-1990; cuid3040; 213696 (Box I:13, Folder 11)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Lani Maestro), 1988-1991; cuid3041; 213695 (Box I:13, Folder 12)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Rejections), 1990-1991; cuid3042; 213694 (Box I:13, Folder 13)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Toronto/Halifax Notes, Lists and Other Miscellaneous, 1990-1991; cuid3043; 213693 (Box I:13, Folder 14)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Keith Piper), 1990 August-1991 January; cuid3044; 213692 (Box I:13, Folder 15)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Donald Rodney), 1990; cuid3045; 213691 (Box I:13, Folder 16)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Art, 1988-Circa 1991; cuid3046; 213690 (Box I:13, Folder 17)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Floor Plan, 1991; cuid3047; 213689 (Box I:13, Folder 18)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Research, Undated; cuid3048; 213688 (Box I:13, Folder 19)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Research (2 of 2), 1987-1990; cuid3049; 213687 (Box I:13, Folder 20)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue, Circa 1989-1991; cuid3050; 213686 (Box I:13, Folder 21)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue (Maharaj Essay Draft), 1990-1991; cuid3051; 213685 (Box I:13, Folder 22)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue, 1991; cuid3052; 213684 (Box I:13, Folder 23)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Text, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3053; 213683 (Box I:13, Folder 24)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Text for II, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3054; 213682 (Box I:13, Folder 25)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Programming for II, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3055; 213681 (Box I:13, Folder 26)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- July 1990 London Research (1 of 2), 1988-1991; cuid3056; 213680 (Box I:13, Folder 27)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- July 1990 London Research (2 of 2), 1988-1991; cuid3057; 213679 (Box I:13, Folder 28)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Installation, 1991; cuid3058; 213678 (Box I:13, Folder 29)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Checklist, Installation and Packing Instructions, 1990-1993; cuid3059; 213677 (Box I:13, Folder 30)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Materials for Venue Book, 1991-1992; cuid3060; 213676 (Box I:13, Folder 31)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Press, 1991 March-1993 January; cuid3061; 213675 (Box I:13, Folder 32)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Duke Press, 1993 January; cuid3062; 213674 (Box I:13, Folder 33)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Madison Art Center, 1991 March-1992 August; cuid3063; 213673 (Box I:13, Folder 34)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Madison Press Materials, 1991-1992; cuid3064; 213672 (Box I:13, Folder 35)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Miami Press Materials, 1992 June-July; cuid3065; 213671 (Box I:13, Folder 36)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- MFA Press Materials (Boston), 1991-1992; cuid3066; 213670 (Box I:13, Folder 37)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Walker Art Center Press, 1992; cuid3067; 213669 (Box I:13, Folder 38)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Notes and Miscellaneous Items, 1990 July-1991 March; cuid3068; 213668 (Box I:13, Folder 39)
  - Luis Caballero, 1982-1991; cuid3069; 213667 (Box I:13, Folder 40)
  - Hope Sandrow, 1991; cuid3070; 213666 (Box I:13, Folder 41)
  - Hope Sandrow -- General Idea, 1991; cuid3071; 213665 (Box I:13, Folder 42)
  - General Idea, Circa 1991; cuid3072; 213664 (Box I:13, Folder 43)
  - Caballero/Sandrow/General Idea, 1991 May-October; cuid3073; 213663 (Box I:13, Folder 44)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Checklists, 1990-1991; cuid3074; 213662 (Box I:13, Folder 45)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Installation (1 of 2), 1991; cuid3075; 213661 (Box I:13, Folder 46)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Installation (2 of 2), 1991; cuid3076; 213660 (Box I:13, Folder 47)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (1 of 3), 1988-1991; cuid3077; 213659 (Box I:13, Folder 48)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (2 of 3), 1990-1991; cuid3078; 213658 (Box I:14, Folder 1)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (3 of 3), 1985-1991; cuid3079; 213657 (Box I:14, Folder 2)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Questions, 1988; cuid3080; 213656 (Box I:14, Folder 3)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Tour Materials, Circa 1990-1991; cuid3081; 213655 (Box I:14, Folder 4)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Public Relations, Circa 1983-1991; cuid3082; 213654 (Box I:14, Folder 5)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Press, 1991 July-September; cuid3083; 213653 (Box I:14, Folder 6)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibition -- Plan and Proposal, 1989-1990; cuid3084; 213652 (Box I:14, Folder 7)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibit -- Captions, CIrca 1991-1992; cuid3085; 213651 (Box I:14, Folder 8)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibit -- Press, 1991 November 26; cuid3086; 213650 (Box I:14, Folder 9)
  - Aids Bottle Project, 1991; cuid3087; 213649 (Box I:14, Folder 10)
  - Tomie Arai (Window Installation), 1991 September-December; cuid3088; 213648 (Box I:14, Folder 11)
  - Michael Andrews -- Lists, Labels, Text and Other Miscellaneous, 1986-1991; cuid3089; 213647 (Box I:14, Folder 12)
  - Michael Andrews -- Printed Reseach, 1980-1991; cuid3090; 213646 (Box I:14, Folder 13)
  - Michael Andrews -- Press, 1992 January-1995 July; cuid3091; 213645 (Box I:14, Folder 14)
  - Spinster's Tale (Windows) -- Lindsey Walt, 1991 November-1992 June; cuid3092; 213644 (Box I:14, Folder 15)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1990, cuid3093; 213643 (Box I:14, Folder 16)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1991, cuid3094; 213642 (Box I:14, Folder 17)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1992, cuid3095; 213641 (Box I:14, Folder 18)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1993, cuid3096; 213640 (Box I:14, Folder 19)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1994, cuid3097; 213639 (Box I:14, Folder 20)
  - A Day Without Art -- Visual Aids Ribbon Project, 1989-1992; cuid3098; 213638 (Box I:14, Folder 21)
  - A Day Without Art -- Press, 1989-1993; cuid3099; 213637 (Box I:14, Folder 22)
  - A Day Without Art -- Publicity Packet, 1989-1991; cuid3100; 213636 (Box I:14, Folder 23)
  - Elaine Reichek: Native Intelligence -- Biography and Slides, Circa 1990-1992; cuid3101; 213635 (Box I:14, Folder 24)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Catalogue, Circa 1991-1992; cuid3102; 213634 (Box I:14, Folder 25)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Errata Sheets, Undated; cuid3103; 213633 (Box I:14, Folder 26)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Installation, Circa 1991-1993; cuid3104; 213632 (Box I:14, Folder 27)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Lists and Installation, Circa 1991-1992; cuid3105; 213631 (Box I:14, Folder 28)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Condition, 1990-1993; cuid3106; 213630 (Box I:14, Folder 29)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Press and Photo Material, 1989 February-1993 May; cuid3107; 213629 (Box I:14, Folder 30)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Drafts, Notes and Other Miscellaneous, Circa 1989-1993; cuid3108; 213628 (Box I:14, Folder 31)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Schedule (Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art), 1992 November-1993 April; cuid3109; 213627 (Box I:14, Folder 32)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Western Washington University, 1992 October-1993 April; cuid3110; 213626 (Box I:14, Folder 33)
  - Lily van der Stokker (Small Gallery), 1989 October-1992 March; cuid3111; 213625 (Box I:14, Folder 34)
  - Arne Svenson (Windows), 1989 August-1992 March; cuid3112; 213624 (Box I:14, Folder 35)
  - Opulent Past -- Artifact Copies (1 of 2), 1992; cuid3113; 213623 (Box I:14, Folder 36)
  - Opulent Past -- Artifact Copies (2 of 2), 1992; cuid3114; 213622 (Box I:14, Folder 37)
  - Opulent Past -- Catalogue, 1992; cuid3115; 213621 (Box I:14, Folder 38)
  - Opulent Past -- Installation, 1992 April-May; cuid3116; 213620 (Box I:14, Folder 39)
  - Opulent Past -- Invitations, 1992; cuid3117; 213619 (Box I:14, Folder 40)
  - Opulent Past -- Press, 1992 June-1993 November; cuid3118; 213618 (Box I:14, Folder 41)
  - John Kohring (Small Gallery), 1990 October-1992 May; cuid3119; 213617 (Box I:14, Folder 42)
  - Michael Richards (Windows), 1992 February-December; cuid3120; 213616 (Box I:14, Folder 43)
  - Camera As Weapon, 1992; cuid3121; 213615 (Box I:14, Folder 44)
  - Camera As Weapon -- Press, 1992 September-November; cuid3122; 213614 (Box I:14, Folder 45)
  - Adrian Piper: Decide Who You Are, 1991 August-1992 July; cuid3123; 213613 (Box I:14, Folder 46)
  - Adrian Piper -- Magazine, 1993 September-October; cuid3124; 213612 (Box I:14, Folder 47)
  - Jeff Gates (Windows), 1989 April-1992 August; cuid3125; 213611 (Box I:14, Folder 48)
  - Australian AIDS Posters, 1992 September-1996 December; cuid3126; 213610 (Box I:14, Folder 49)
  - Hugh Steers (Small Gallery), 1990-1992; cuid3127; 213609 (Box I:14, Folder 50)
  - Gotscho -- Correspondence, 1991 October-1993 January; cuid3128; 213608 (Box I:15, Folder 1)
  - Gotscho -- Biographies, Circa 1992-1993; cuid3129; 213607 (Box I:15, Folder 2)
  - Gotscho -- Exhibit [Installation], Circa 1991-1993; cuid3130; 213606 (Box I:15, Folder 3)
  - Gotscho -- Public Relations, 1992 April-1993 March; cuid3131; 213605 (Box I:15, Folder 4)